{
    "translations": {
      "en": {
        "fa1": "../../../AV/VisFormalLang/NFA/AutomataFiles/NFA2DFA2a.jff",
        "q1": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
          "question": "sets may contain duplicated elements.",
          "answer": ["False"],
          "choices": ["True", "False"]
        },
        "q2": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
          "question": "Let P = {7, 11, 42}, Which of the following is correct?",
          "answer": ["P = {11, 42, 7}"],
          "choices": ["P = {11, 42, 7}", "P  ≠ {11, 42, 7}"]
        },
        "q3": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question": "Let P = {7, 11, 42}, what is the base type of P elements?",
          "answer": ["Integers"],
          "choices": ["Integers", "Real numbers"]
        },
        "q4": {
          "type": "select",
          "question": "Let P = {a, b, c, {d, e}, {f}}. Which of the following is an element in the set.",
          "answer": ["a","b","c","{d, e}","{f}"],
          "choices": ["a","b", "c", "d", "e","{d}","{d, e}","f","{f}"]
        },
        "q5": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question": "Which of the following is a valid set:",
          "answer": "{a, 2, 3}",
          "choices": ["1, 2, 3", "{a, 2, 3}"]
        },
        "q6": {
          "type": "textBox",
          "question": "Describe the previous set using your own words.",
          "answer": "yes"
        },
        "q7": {
          "type": "select",
          "question": "Let P = {a, b, c}, which of the following is ∉P",
          "answer": ["b", "{a, b, c}"],
          "choices": ["a", "{a}", "b", "{a, b, c}"]
        },
        "q8": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question": "Which of the following ∈Q?",
          "answer": "a",
          "choices": ["a", "1", "{a,b}", "Q has no elements because it is the null set."]
        },
        "q9": {
          "type": "textBox",
          "question": "What does it mean to say that |P| = 3?",
          "answer": "P has 3 elements"
        },
        "q10": {
          "type": "select",
          "question": "Let P = {x|x is a positive integer}. Which of the following is a subset of P?",
          "answer": ["{1, 2, 3}", "{x|x is an even number}", "{x|x is a prime number}"],
          "choices": ["{1, 2, 3}", "{x|x is an even number}", "{x|x is a real number}", "{x|x is a prime number}"]
        },
        "q11": {
          "type": "textBox",
          "question": "let $w=abbc$, and $v=ab$. What is $|vv^Rw|$",
          "answer": "8"
        },
        "q12": {
          "type": "select",
          "question": "Which of the following are strings in $\\Sigma∗$?",
          "answer": ["$\\lambda$", "a", "b", "aa", "abbabb"],
          "choices": ["$\\lambda$", "a", "b", "aa", "abbabb", "aaabababcc"]
        },
        "q12_1": {
          "type": "select",
          "question": "Which are examples of $w*$ where $w = abc$?",
          "answer": ["$Λ$", "$abc$", "$abcabc$"],
          "choices": ["$Λ$", "$abc$", "$abcabc$", "$aabbcc$"]
        },
        "q13": {
          "type": "select",
          "question": "Let  $\\lambda$ = {$a,b$}, Which of the following are strings in ?",
          "answer": ["$a$", "$b$", "$aa$", "$abbabb$"],
          "choices": [
            "$\\lambda$",
            "$a$",
            "$b$",
            "$aa$",
            "$abbabb$",
            "$aaabababcc$"
          ]
        },
        "q14": {
          "type": "textBox",
          "question": " Let $\\sigma$={$a$,$b$,$c$}, $L1$={$ab$,$bc$,$aba$}, $L2$={$c$,$bc$,$bcc$}, What is $L1∪L2$ ?",
          "answer": "ab,bc,aba,c,bcc"
        },
        "q15": {
          "type": "textBox",
          "question": "Let $\\Sigma$={$a$,$b$,$c$}, $L1$={$ab$,$bc$,$aba$}, $L2$={$c$,$bc$,$bcc$}, What is $L1∩L2$ ?",
          "answer": "{bc}"
        },
        "q16": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question": "What is ?",
          "answer": [" "],
          "choices": [" "]
        },
        "q17": {
          "type": "textBox",
          "question": "What states can be combined?",
          "answer": "{abc,abbc,abbcc,bcc,bcbc,bcbcc,abac,ababc,ababcc}"
        },
        "q18": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question": "Let $\\Sigma$={$a$,$b$}, $L1$={$ab$,$aba$}, What is $L0$?",
          "answer": ["{$λ$}"],
          "choices": ["{$λ$}", "{}<Empty set>", "$λ$"]
        },
        "q19": {
          "type": "textBox",
          "question": "Let $\\Sigma$={$a$,$b$}, $L1$={$ab$,$aba$}, What is $L2$? ",
          "answer": "{abab, ababa, abaab, abaaba}"
        },
        "q19_1": {
          "type": "textBox",
          "question": "Let $\\Sigma$={$a$,$b$}, $L1$={$ab$,$aba$}, What is $L3$?",
          "answer": "{ababab, ababaab, abaabab, abaabaab, abababa, ababaaba, abaababa, abaabaaba}"
        }
      }
    }
  }
  